<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Meetly_Clone</string>

    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="text_English">English</string>
    <string name="text_hint_Email">Email</string>
    <string name="text_hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="text_hint_Repassword">Re-Password</string>
    <string name="btn_text_Register">Register</string>
    <string name="text_register">Register</string>
    <string name="text_forget_pass">Forget password</string>
    <string name="text_Meetly">Meetly</string>
    <string name="text_btn_Loginwithfb">Login with facebook</string>
    <string name="text_btn_CreateAccount">Create Account</string>
    <string name="text_dontpost">We don\'t post anything to Facebook.</string>
    <string name="text_terms">By Signing in,You agree to our <b>Terms of Service</b> and <b>Privacy policy.</b> </string>
    <string name="text_Community">Community</string>
    <string name="text_CommunityGuidelines">Community Guidelines</string>
    <string name="text_SafetyTips">Safety Tips</string>
    <string name="text_Legal">Legal</string>
    <string name="text_PrivacyPolicy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="text_Licenses">Licenses</string>
    <string name="text_Termsofservice">Terms of service</string>
    <string name="text_SelectLanguage">Select language</string>
    <string name="text_Logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="text_Deleteaccount">Delete account</string>
    <string name="text_AppSetting">App setting</string>


    <string name="tv_meetly">Meetly</string>
    <string name="et_english">English</string>
    <string name="tv_register">Register</string>
    <string name="et_email">E-mail</string>
    <string name="et_password">Password</string>
    <string name="btn_login">Login</string>
    <string name="tv_forgetpassword">Forget Password</string>
    <string name="btn_login_with_facebook">Login with Facebook</string>
    <string name="tv_don_post">We don not post anything on facebook.</string>
    <string name="tv_by_syning">By signing in, you agree to our</string>
    <string name="tv_terms">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="tv_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="tv_and">and</string>
    <string name="et_name">Name</string>
    <string name="tv_this_is_how_appear_in_meetly">This is how appear in meetly</string>
    <string name="tv_enter_email">Please enter your email in order to recover your account later</string>
    <string name="et_dob">DD/MM/YYYY</string>
    <string name="tv_public_age">Your age will be public</string>
    <string name="et_gender">Your Gender</string>
    <string name="tv_cannot_change">You cannot change your gender after create account</string>
    <string name="tv_sign_up">Sign-Up</string>
    <string name="tv_login">Login</string>
    <string name="btn_create_account">Create Account</string>
    <string name="tv_term_of_service">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="tv_forget_password">Forget Password</string>
    <string name="tv_hotmeet">hotmeet</string>
    <string name="et_repassword">Re-Password</string>
    <string name="btn_save">Save</string>
    <string name="tv_privacy_policy_information">
        Free Best Match App built the hotmeet app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by Free Best Match App at no cost and is intended for use as is.

This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.

If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that I collect is used for providing and improving the Service. I will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at [hotmeet] unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.

Information Collection and Use

For a better experience, while using our Service, I may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The information that I request will be retained on your device and is not collected by me in any way.

The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.

Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app

Google Play Services
AdMob
Firebase Analytics
Firebase Crashlytics
Facebook
Log Data

I want to inform you that whenever you use my Service, in a case of an error in the app I collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing my Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.

Cookies

Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on your device is internal memory.

This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collect information and improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.

Service Providers

I may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:

To facilitate our Service;
To provide the Service on our behalf;
To perform Service-related services; or
To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
I want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.

Security

I value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and I cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Links to Other Sites

This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by me. Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. I have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

Children’s Privacy

These Services do not address anyone under the age of 18. I do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 18. In the case I discover that a child under 18 has provided me with personal information, I immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact me so that I will be able to do necessary actions.

Changes to This Privacy Policy

I may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.

Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions about my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact me at hotmeetdating@gmail.com.
    </string>
    <string name="get_premium_get_15_discount">Get Premium Get 15% Discount</string>
    <string name="tv_15">15%</string>
    <string name="tv_500_coin">500 coin</string>
    <string name="tv_rs_280_00">Rs 280.00</string>
    <string name="tv_buy_now">Buy Now</string>
    <string name="tv_2000_coin">2000 coin</string>
    <string name="tv_rs_1100_00">Rs 1100.00</string>
    <string name="tv_5000_coin">5000 coin</string>
    <string name="tv_rs_2200_00">Rs 2200.00</string>
    <string name="tv_8500_coin">8500 coin</string>
    <string name="tv_rs_3550_00">Rs 3550.00</string>
    <string name="tv_12500_coin">12500 coin</string>
    <string name="tv_rs_4900_00">Rs 4900.00</string>
    <string name="tv_35000_coin">35000 coin</string>
    <string name="tv_rs_11000_00">Rs 11000.00</string>
    <string name="tv_buy_coins">Buy Coins</string>
    <string name="tv_earn_free_coin">EARN FREE COINS</string>
    <string name="tv_0_coin">0 Coins</string>
    <string name="tv_unlock_feature_string">Coins unlock feature like extra begels and the ability to view mutual friend</string>
    <string name="tv_community_guideline">Community Guidelines</string>
    <string name="tv_welcome_to_hotmeet_community">Welcome to the hotmeet community.</string>
    <string name="tv_licence">Licenses</string>
    <string name="tv_hotmeet_community_information">Welcome to the hotmeet community.

If you’re honest, kind and respectful to others, you’ll always be welcome here. If you choose not to
        be, you may not last. Our goal is to allow users to express themselves freely as long as it
        doesn’t offend others. Everyone is held to the same standard on hotmeet. We’re asking you 
        to be considerate, think before you act, and abide by our community guidelines both on and
        offline. Seriously, don’t make us Swipe Left on you—because there will be no do-overs once 
        we do.

Nudity or Sexual Content hotmeet wasn’t invented to show off your six most provocative photos. 
        Seriously. We’re not asking you to comb your hair to one side and put on your Sunday best; 
        just try to keep it classy and appropriate for public consumption. No nudity, no sexually
        explicit content, no sex toys. Also, if you choose to sport a thong, please note: suggestive
        poses are not allowed on hotmeet. (If it’s in the Kamasutra, it probably shouldn’t be in 
        your profile pic.) Photos that violate these guidelines may be deleted, and the most severe
        cases may result in account removal. Inappropriateness If you wouldn’t say it to someone’s 
        face, don’t say it on hotmeet. Keep in mind, there is a human being on the other end of your
        screen. Be respectful with anyone you interact with in the hotmeet community. If you are 
        disrespectful, offensive, threatening or rude to another user, we reserve the right to ban
        you from hotmeet. Violent or Graphic Content We do not tolerate violent, graphic or obscene
        photos or profiles containing hate speech on hotmeet, and will remove any such content that 
        we identify. Any content that we deem disrespectful to others in the community may be
        removed, and the user banned, depending on its severity. With this in mind, please exercise
        restraint and respect for others in the community when posting hunting photos, as many users 
        find images of dead animals disturbing. Hate We have a zero-tolerance policy on hate speech.
        Any content that promotes or condones violence against individuals or groups based on race
        or ethnicity, religion, disability, gender, age, nationality, sexual orientation or gender 
        identity is strictly forbidden and may result in you being permanently banned. Children 
        Unattended Standard supermarket rules apply. No children unaccompanied by an adult — in this 
        case, we’re talking about your profile photos. Even if it’s you at age seven and it’s the
        cutest you ever. This is to protect kids. Their safety is more important than your
        adorableness of years past — we reserve the right to remove these photos. Harassment Any
        reports of stalking, threats, bullying, intimidation, invading privacy, or revealing other 
        people's personal information are taken very seriously. That means no taking screenshots of
        other people’s profiles or conversations and posting or distributing them publicly. hotmeet 
        reserves the right to ban any user that has exhibited behavior that is threatening,
        intentionally malicious, or harmful to other users. Children Unattended Standard supermarket
        rules apply. No children unaccompanied by an adult — in this case, we’re talking about your 
        profile photos. Even if it’s you at age seven and it’s the cutest you ever. This is to 
        protect kids. Their safety is more important than your adorableness of years past — we
        reserve the right to remove these photos. Scamming hotmeet has a zero-tolerance policy on
        predatory behavior of any kind. Anyone attempting to get other users’ private information 
        for fraudulent or illegal activity may be banned. Also, any user caught sharing their own 
        financial account information (PayPal, Venmo, etc.) for the purpose of receiving money from
        other users may be banned from hotmeet. Copyright Infringement If it doesn’t belong to you,
        it doesn’t belong on your hotmeet profile. Any of your profile content that someone else 
        owns the copyright to (and has not granted you authorization to use) may be deleted. Phone 
        Numbers or Private Information No, we don’t need your digits. Please do not publish a phone
        number on your profile. hotmeet invented the double opt-in, (two people have to swipe right 
        on each other to connect), so that personal information can be shared privately, if desired,
        and not broadcast publicly. Private information of any sort, such as phone numbers, social 
        security numbers, addresses, passwords or financial information is subject to removal and may
        result in you being banned from hotmeet
</string>

    <string name="tv_safty_tips">Safety Tips</string>

    <string name="tv_safety_tips_information">
        Dating Safely hotmeet brings people together. With more than 20 billion matches made to date
        and millions of new matches made daily, our community is constantly growing. With so many
        people on hotmeet, user safety is a priority. We understand that meeting someone for the
        first time whether online, through an acquaintance or on an outing is intriguing and exciting.
        However, your safety is very important, and because you are in control of your hotmeet
        experience, there are certain safety steps that you should follow while dating – both online
        and offline. We ask you to read the tips and information below, and strongly urge you to
        follow these guidelines in the interest of your personal safety and well-being. However, you
        are always the best judge of your own safety, and these guidelines are not intended to be a
        substitute for your own judgment. Online Behavior Protect Your Finances and Never Send Money
        or Financial Information Never respond to any request to send money, especially overseas or
        via wire transfer, and report it to us immediately – even if the person claims to be in an
        emergency. Wiring money is like sending cash: the sender has no protections against loss and
        it’s nearly impossible to reverse the transaction or trace the money. For more information,
        click on the video below to the U.S. Federal Trade Commissions advice to avoid online dating
        scams, also available here. Protect Your Personal Information Never give personal information,
        such as: your social security number, credit card number or bank information, or your work or
        home address to people you don’t know or haven’t met in person. Note: hotmeet will never send
        you an email asking for your username and password information. Any such communication should
        be reported immediately. Be Web Wise Block and report suspicious users. You can block and
        report concerns about any suspicious user anonymously at any time on hotmeet – while swiping
        or after you’ve matched. Keep conversations on the platform. Bad actors will try to move the
        conversation to text, personal email or phone conversations. Report All Suspicious Behavior
        Additionally, please report anyone who violates our terms of use. Examples of terms of use
        violations include: Asks you for money or donations Requesting photographs. Minors using the
        platform Users sending harassing or offensive messages Users behaving inappropriately after
        meeting in person Fraudulent registration or profiles. Spam or solicitation, such as
        invitations to call 1-900 numbers or attempts to sell products or services. Offline Behavior
        First meetings are exciting, but always take precautions and follow these guidelines to help
        you stay safe: Get to Know the Other Person Keep your communications limited to the platform
        and really get to know users online/using the app before meeting them in person. Bad actors
        often push people to communicate off the platform immediately. It’s up to you to research
        and do your due diligence. Always Meet and Stay in Public Meet for the first time in a
        populated, public place – never in a private or remote location, and never at your home or
        apartment. If your date pressures you, end the date and leave at once. Tell Your Friends
        and Family Members of Your Plans Inform a friend or family member of your plans and when
        and where you’re going. Make sure you have your cell phone charged and with you at all times.
        Transport Yourself to and from the Meeting You need to be independent and in control of your
        own transportation, especially in case things don’t work out. Stay Sober Consumption of
        alcohol and/or other drugs can impair your judgment and potentially put you in danger.
        It’s important to keep a clear mind and avoid anything that might place you at risk. Be aware
        that bad actors might try to take advantage of you by altering your beverage(s) with synthetic
        substances. Health hotmeet welcomes everyone and empowers our community of users to create
        and cultivate relationships. An important aspect of any healthy relationship though – whether
        formed on hotmeet or otherwise – is ensuring proper sexual health and safety. And as a member
        of the hotmeet community it is your responsibility to make sure you do the following, if you
        choose to engage in sexual activity. Protect Yourself. You and your partner should use proper
        protection. Condoms and other mechanisms can significantly reduce the risk of contracting or
        passing on an STI, such as HIV. To be effective, however, protective measures must be used
        consistently. Please keep in mind, you can still get certain STIs, like herpes or HPV from
        contact with your partner’s skin even when using a condom. Be Open and Honest It is completely
        reasonable to have a conversation with your partner regarding sex and sexual contact before
        actually having it. All issues ranging from the number of partners each of you has had, to
        the last time each of you was tested for STIs are fair game. Many STIs are curable or
        treatable. If either you or your partner has an STI that is curable, you both need to start
        treatment to avoid becoming re-infected. It is important to be completely honest in these
        conversations. Vaccinate The risk of contracting some STIs can be reduced through vaccination.
        Talk to your doctor or a professional at a sexual health clinic to learn more.
    </string>

    <string name="tv_licenses_information">
        Below is a non-exhaustive list of trademarks and service marks owned by Edicosglobal Digital
        S.L. related to the hotmeet brand. You may not use the below marks without authorization
        from Edicosglobal Digital S.L.. If granted authorization and you use the below marks in
        publications distributed only in the United States, include the appropriate ™ or ® symbol
        on at least the first use and on those subsequent uses where the marks appear prominently.
        For publications distributed outside the United States, use of the ™ notice symbol is
        acceptable. It is also appropriate to use, instead of the trademark symbols, the trademark
        legends in the forms listed below: Sample trademark legends:
        1) For registered trademarks:
        hotmeet is the exclusive registered trademark of Edicosglobal Digital S.L., and is used with permission.
        2) For unregistered trademarks: hotmeet is the exclusive trademark of Edicosglobal Digital S.L., and is used with permission.
    </string>

</resources>